A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 3 FA1554
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1952, 1972-1973, 1980-2012; 2; 18.27 Cubic Feet 38 legal document boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Medical Center, Fudan University (Shanghai Medical College), Technology Assessment, 96-658, 1996-1997, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Medical College of Dornogobi (Sainshand Medical College), Advancement of Medial Education, 94-610, 1994-1997, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - China Ministry of Education, 1992, 1994-1998, 2003, 2007, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Myanmar, 1996, 2008-2009, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, 1989-1993, 1995-1999, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 183-184)
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, CMB Reports, Lincoln Chan, 2006 December 12 (Box 15, Folder 183)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, Power Point Presentations to President of CMB (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, CMB Presentations, Myanmar Presenations (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, Ministry of Health, Health Professions Education, 90-526, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Myanmar, Department of Medical Sciences, Ministry of Health, Health Professions Education, 93-599, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - National University of Laos, Reform of Medical Education, 93-589, 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - National University of Laos, Staff and Curriculum Development, 99-709, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - National University of Laos, Staff and Library Development, 91-552, 1991-1999 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Community Health Professionals, 98-691, 1998-2006 (Box 16, Folder 190-191)
  - Nursing Education, Stanford University Medical Center, American Nursing Schools, CM275, 1952, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Biomedical Writing and Editing, 95-614, 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Biomedical Writing and Editing, 01-743, 1995, 2000-2007 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), China Medicine and Public Health Institute Conference, 04-800, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Chinese Health Policy Institute, 02-770, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 196-197)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Comprehensive Medical Education, 98-670, 1998-1999, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Conference on Family Medicine, 05-811, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Conference on Medical Professionals, 00-724, 1999-2004 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Faculty Development, 98-669, 1998-2004 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Human Clinical Trials, 01-744, 1998, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Improve Clinical Skills in China, 02-774, 2002-2006 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Leadership Training, 00-736, 2000-2006 (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Medical Ethics, 98-672, 1984, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Needs Assessment Survey, 02-773, 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), On-Line Medical Education, 98-671, 1998-2003 (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Private Medical School, 01-745, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), SARS Prevention, 03-784, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Twin Registry, 01-746, 2000-2001, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1999 President's Council, 98-686 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Alzheimer's Dementia Studies, 99-699, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 212-213)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Chinese Academic Urban Health Care System, 99-706, 1999-2006 (Box 19, Folder 214-215)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Consultant, Carol Aschenbrener, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Consultant, Gerald Lazarus, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 217-218)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Education Center for Genomic Medicine, 03-785, 2003-2007 (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Genomic Diversity, 98-675, 1998-2005 (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Genomic Diversity, 98-675, 1998-2005 (Box 20, Folder 221)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Grants Management, 01-747, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Hepatitis Grant, 93-582 review, 96-650, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), HIV Education Program, 98-686, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), HIV/AIDS Training, 99-700, 1999-2004 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Hypertension Genetics, 96-657, 1996-2002 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Knowledge Discovery Center, 03-787, 2003-2007 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Merger Consultancy, 1998 January 17-25, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), National Medical Education Forum, 1998 June 1-2, 92-579, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Osteoporosis, 97-667, 1996-2006 (Box 21, Folder 230)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Parasitology, 98-674, 1995-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 231-234)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), President's Meeting, 1997 November 10-11 (Box 21, Folder 235)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Remodeling Medical Education, 03-788, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 236)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Small Grants Program, 02-777, 2002, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 237)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Stem Cell Biology, 01-748, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 238)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Strengthening Med-Surgical Nursing, 92-580, 1995, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 239)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Symposium on Medical Education Research, 88-503, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 240)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Training Program for Clinical Faculty, 98-673, 1998-2006 (Box 22, Folder 241)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Workshop on Medical Library, 88-503, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Workshop on Nursing Curricula, 92-579, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Viral Hepatitis Meeting, 1992 April 22 and May 10, 88-503 (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Philips, Michael, Publications, 1994, 1998, 2000, 2002, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 245)
  - Qinghua, Tsinghua University, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 246)
  - Sainshand Medical College, Community Health Training, 02-772, 2002-2007 (Box 23, Folder 247)
  - Sainshand Medical College, Medical Education, 95-624, 1995-1997, 1999-2004 (Box 23, Folder 248)
  - Shanghai Medical University, China Medical Board Presidents' Meeting, 1994 May 17-18, 92-579, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 249)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Health Management Training Center, 96-629, 1995-2007 (Box 23, Folder 250-251)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Primary Liver Cancer, 93-583, 1993-1998, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 252)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Regional Program/Educational Material, 1998 May 26-29, 92-579, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 253)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Conference of Leaders, 1992 September 18-20, 92-554, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Cord Blood Transplantation, 96-630, 1996-2004 (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Faculty and Doctoral Students Training, 04-808, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Nasopharyngeal Cancer, 98-678, 1998-2001, 2003-2006 (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Nurse Consultant, 98-668, 1998, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 258)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Nursing Education, 98-692, 1998-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 259)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Paraplegia, 01-759, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 260)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Planning Grant, Trauma Center, 98-686, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 261)
  - Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Program on Higher Nursing Education Development (POHNED), 88-503, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 262)
  - Thai Universities, 2005, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 263)
  - Tibet Medical College, Clinical Practice Bases, 98-693, 1998-2004 (Box 25, Folder 264)
  - Tibet Medical College, Workshop on Curriculum, 1993 February, 92-570, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 265)
  - Tribhuvan University, Institute of Medicine, Communication Learning Network, 00-720, 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 266)
  - Tsinghua University, AIDS/SARS Summit, 98-686, 1998-2003 (Box 25, Folder 267)
  - Ulaan Baatar Medical College, 1993, 2000-2002, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 268)
  - United States-China Education Institute, Building a Common Ground, 90-552, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 269)
  - University of Indonesia, Problem Solving Workshop, 1996 January 18-20, 92-579, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - West China University of Medical Education, National Meeting on Medical Education and Research, 94-609, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 271-272)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, Clinical Skiils, 91-542, 1991, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, Consultant, Keith Blaynay, 92-580, 1990-1992, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 274-275)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, English Skills Training, 00-738, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, Living Tendon, 98-682, 1998, 2000-2006 (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, Nursing Textbooks, 00-739, 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, Program of Radiology and Nuclear Medicine, 93-584, 1993, 1995-2001, 2003-2007 (Box 27, Folder 279)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, 3 Year Medical Education, 91-551, 1991, 1993-1999 (Box 27, Folder 280)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, 3 Year Medical Education, 96-661, 1996-1997, 1999-2000, 2002-2006 (Box 27, Folder 281)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, 3 Year Medical Education, Textbooks, 97-666, 1997-2006 (Box 27, Folder 282)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Bilingual Nursing Textbooks, 02-768, 2000, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 283)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Clinical Engineering, 98-684, 1998-2006 (Box 27, Folder 284)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Continuing Medical Educatioon, 97-664, 1997-2005 (Box 27, Folder 285-286)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Program on Higher Nursing Education Development (POHNED), 96-695, 1998-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 287-288)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Genes and Hypertension, 01-761, 2000-2001, 2003-2006 (Box 28, Folder 289)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Healt Administrtion for Minority Regions, 92-572, 1992-1998, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 290)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Masters Degree in Public Health, 98-683, 1997-2001, 2003-2007 (Box 28, Folder 291)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Maternal and Child Health, 96-631, 1996, 1998-2004 (Box 28, Folder 292)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Network for Medical Education, 00-731, 2000-2006 (Box 28, Folder 293)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Program on Higher Nursing Education Development (POHNED), 93-597, 1993-2000 (Box 29, Folder 294-295)
  - Xi'an Jiaotong University, School of Medicine, Womeen's Reproductive Health, 01-762, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 296)
  - Xi'an Medical University, Continuation Medical Education, 88-503, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 297)
  - Xi'an Medical University, President's Meeing, 1992 March 14, 88-503, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 298)
  - Xi'an Medical University & Tibet Medical College, Problem Solving Workshop, 1995 May, 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 299-300)
  - Xiangya Scchool of Medicine (Hunan Medical University), Drug Metabolism, 99-697, 1999-2006 (Box 29, Folder 301)
  - Xiangya Scchool of Medicine (Hunan Medical University), Drug Metabolism, 99-697, 1999-2006 (Box 30, Folder 302-303)
  - Xiangya Scchool of Medicine (Hunan Medical University), Gene Diagnosis and Therapy, 99-698, 1998-2007 (Box 30, Folder 304-305)
  - Xiangya Scchool of Medicine (Hunan Medical University), Nasopharngeal Cancer, 96-655, 1995-2004 (Box 30, Folder 306)
  - Xiangya Scchool of Medicine (Hunan Medical University), Senior Health Aministration, 00-727, 1999-2005 (Box 30, Folder 307)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Cancer Screening, 92-559, 1991-1999, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 308)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), China Medical Board President's Meeting, 1991 April 26-28, 88-503 (Box 30, Folder 309)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Clinical Skills Program, 91-543, 1991-2000, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 310)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Computer-Assisted Instruction (CAI) in Medical Education, 99-703, 1999-2008 (Box 31, Folder 311)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Distance Adult Medical Education, 99-704, 1999-2008 (Box 31, Folder 312)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Sino-Thailand Senior Health Executives Study and Exchange Project, 07-873, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 313)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Undergraduate amd Postgraduate Education in Family Medicine, 98-696, 1998-2007 (Box 31, Folder 314)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Westlake Forum on China's Health Policy, 06-847, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 315)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), Women's Health and Society, 93-586, 1992-2003, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 316)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU)/Jiujiang Medical University (JMU)/West China University, Medical School (WCUMS), Clinical teaching & Assessment of Clinical Competence, 1990-1992 (Box 31, Folder 317)
  - Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), China Medical Board (CMB) Progress Reports, Zhejiang Medial University (ZMU), 2000 September (Box 31, Folder 318)
  - Central South University, Xiangya School of Medicine, Community Based Model for Suicide Prevention, 02-776, 2002-2008 (Box 32, Folder 319)
  - Central South University, Xiangya School of Medicine, Central South University (CSU) Demostrtive Lab on Pharmacogenetics, 01-755, 2001-2007 (Box 32, Folder 320-321)
  - Central South University, Xiangya School of Medicine, Immunoglobulin-like Molecules Eduation Program, 04-799, 2002-2008 (Box 32, Folder 322)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Conference on the Future of Nursing in Asia, 06-848, 2006-2008 (Box 32, Folder 323-324)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Conference on the Future of Nursing in Asia, 06-848, 2006-2008 (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Development of a Center of Excellence in Nursing Education, 02-771, 2002-2008 (Box 33, Folder 326-327)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Development of Education for Occupational Health Nursing, 99-717, 1999-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 328)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Nursing Assessment in Laos PDR and Vietnam, 09-952, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 329)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Program on Higher Nursing Education Development (POHNED), Update and Assessment Conference, 05-818, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 330)
  - Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing (FON), Program on Higher Nursing Education Development (POHNED), Update and Assessment Conference, 05-818 POHNED Reunion, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 330)
  - China Medical University, Center for Medical Education Development, 03-793, 2003-2007, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 331)
  - Fuddan University, Shanghai Medical College, Pediatric Intensive Care Training, 03-786, 2001-2008 (Box 34, Folder 332)
  - Fuddan University, Shanghai Medical College, Re-Estalishment of the Center of Medical Education Research, 05-819, 2005-2007, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 333)
  - Fuddan University, Shanghai Medical University, Telemedicine Network, 99-701, 1999-2007 (Box 34, Folder 334)
  - Fuddan University, Workshop: Research and Capacity Bulding in Population-based Health in China, 07-870, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 335)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health (SPH), Asian Consutlatin, Education for Global Health Leadership, 08-916, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 336)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health (SPH), Dvelopment of a Field Epidemiological Laboratory for Research and Training Purposes (Chiliab), 99-718, 1999-2007 (Box 34, Folder 337)
  - Hanoi School of Public Health (SPH), Field Epidemiological Laboratory, 05-830, 2005-2007, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 338-339)
  - Hanoi Medical University, Vietnam Family Medicine Development Project, 01-742, 1999-2008 (Box 35, Folder 340-343)
  - Harbin Medical College, Medical Education Reform, 04-806, 2002-2009 (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - Harbin Medical College, Medical Education Reform, 04-806, A Phase Report to CMB, HMU, 2006 September 10 (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - Harbin Medical College, Medical Education Reform, 04-806, 2002-2009 (Box 36, Folder 345)
  - Institute of Medicine, Mandalay, Common Research Laboratory Project, 02-766, 2002-2008 (Box 36, Folder 346)
  - Jiujiang Medical College, Five-Year Rural Medical Education Program, 03-790, 2003-2007 (Box 36, Folder 347)
  - Liverpool School of Tropical Medicine, Support the Participation of Chinese and Vietnamese Researcher to a Writing Workshop, 07-852, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 348)
  - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine, Review of Maternal-Child-Reprouctive Health in Chinese Medical Universities: With Focus on Policy band Health SYstems Sresearh and Education, 08-918, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 349)
  - Mahidol University, Supporting Chinese and Asian Participants to the 4th Asian Pacific Action Alliance on Human Resources for Health (AAAH), 09-957, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 350)
  - National University of Laos, Educational Development, 03-781, 2002-2008 (Box 36, Folder 351-352)
  - Ningxia Medical University, Maternal and Child Health Training, 00-735, 2000-2007 (Box 37, Folder 353)
  - Ningxia Medical University, Maternal and Child Health Training, 00-735, MCH Health Care Training Program of Ningxia Medical College (Box 37, Folder 353)
  - Ningxia Medical University, Maternal and Child Health Training, 00-735, MCH Health Care Training Program of Ningxia Medical College (Box 37, Folder 353)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Maternal and Child Health Training, Phase II, 05-822, 2002, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 354)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Rural Medical Education Workshop, 08-917, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 355)
  - Ningxia Medical College, Rural Medical Education Workshop, 08-917, CMB PPT, 2008 October 23 (Box 37, Folder 355)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Doctoral Summer Course, 09-953, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 356)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Further Research on Chinese Genomic Diversity, 04-805, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 357)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Grants Management Impovement-A Joint Program of the 13 Grantee Schools in China, 05-832, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 358)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Institutional Emergency Medicine Development Initiatives in China, 05-614, 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 359)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) with Johns Hopkins University School of Nursing, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Nursing Doctoral Program, 04-797, 2003-2009 (Box 37, Folder 360-361)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) with Johns Hopkins University School of Nursing, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Nursing Doctoral Program, 04-797, PUMC Student Presentations at JHU SON, Chinese Health Care and Culture, 2006 October 17 (Box 37, Folder 360)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) with Johns Hopkins University School of Nursing, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Nursing Doctoral Program, 04-797, PUMC Student Presentations at JHU SON, Dissertation Summaries, 2006 December 7 (Box 37, Folder 360)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Small Mental Health Grants Program in China, 04-801, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 362)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Study Tour by CMB University Leaders to Universities in United States and United Kingdom, 08-920, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 363)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Training the Trainer, HIV/AIDS, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 364)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Bioethics Leadership Development, 02-769, 2002-2008 (Box 38, Folder 365)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Bioethics Leadership Development, 02-769, CMB Bioethics Leadership Development, 02-769 (Box 38, Folder 366)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Bioethics Leadership Development, 02-769, Bioethics Leadership Development, 02-769 (Box 38, Folder 365)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Continuation of the On-line Medical Education Project, 03-792, 2002-2007 (Box 38, Folder 366)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Human Resources for Health in Rural China, 05-817, 2006-2008 (Box 38, Folder 367-368)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Improving Clinical Education Meeting the Minimal Requirements, 05-817, 2005-2008 (Box 38, Folder 369)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Lancet China Health 21 Initiative, 07-851, 2006-2009 (Box 38, Folder 370)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Lancet China Health 21 Initiative, 07-851, 2006-2009 (Box 39, Folder 371)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), PUHSC-Duke Cardiology Trainig Center, 06-843, 2006-2008 (Box 39, Folder 372)
  - Peking University of Health Science Center (PUHSC), Suicide Research and Prevention Center, Michael Phillips, 09-940, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 373)
  - Shangdong University, Reforming Public Health Education, 08-907, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 374)
  - Shanghai Medical University, Fudan University, Rehabilition Medical Center, 98-676, 1998-2007 (Box 39, Folder 375-376)
  - Sichuan University-West China Universiity of Medical Sciences, Extension of Telemedicine Project to Transmit Medical Courses to Tibet University Medical College, 03-791, 2003-2007, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 377)
  - Sichuan University, Medical Education Center Meeting, 08-919, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 378)
  - Sichuan University, 2008 CMB President's Council Meeting, 08-906 (Box 39, Folder 379)
  - Sichuan University, Public Health Education Reform in China, 04-804, 2002, 2004-2007 (Box 39, Folder 380)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), CMB-SUMS Scholar Prrogram, 98-677, 1998-2007 (Box 40, Folder 381-384)
  - Sun Yat-Sen (Zhongshan) University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), Clinical Skills Learning Center, 05-815, 2004-2008 (Box 40, Folder 385)